mainstreamdata.com 2008-06-22

# Mainstream Data - Privacy Policy

## General

Mainstream Data, Inc. provides the following privacy statement to ensure that all visitors to our Web site, www.mainstreamdata.com are made aware of our policy regarding the collection, use and protection of information supplied to us when visiting this Web site.

Mainstream Data, Inc.. respects your right to privacy and your right to limit information exchanges to only those you initiate. Information gathered on this site is used to serve you better and facilitate use of our Web site.

## Personal Information

At certain points in our Web site, Mainstream Data, Inc. may ask for you to fill out information that pertains to you personally. This type of information can include name, company, title, address, phone number, fax number, email address, etc. At any point that such information is requested, you are always given the choice of whether or not you wish to submit this information to Mainstream Data, Inc.  
Domain Name and IP Address Information

When you visit the Mainstream Data, Inc. Web site, we may also choose to collect information such as the browser you use, and IP addresses, domain names and Uniform Resource Locators ("URLs") of from you access or exit the Web site. Collection of this information occurs automatically when you visit this Web site without requiring any action on your part

There is no connection made to the personal information you provide and the information we gather from the site-specific information. This information is used by Mainstream Data, Inc. for internal purposes only and is used to document and analyze the customer behavior while on our site in order to better understand how visitors navigate through our site, and to measure interest in specific pages. This information is reported internally and then purged when required.  
Cookies

Cookies are small files that a web site places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Portions of this Web site may use cookies in the technical implementation of processes and for providing you with customized information from this Web site. Some browsers can be set to alert you when you are receiving a cookie and to give you the choice to accept or reject the cookie. If you choose not to accept a cookie from this Web site some pages of this Web site may not function properly and you may not be able to connect to our support system and order or download software from our Web site.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Mainstream Data, Inc.. does not sell, trade, or rent to others or non-affiliated companies the personal information we collect from you online.

Mainstream Data, Inc. may provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Mainstream Data, Inc. under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Mainstream Data, Inc.. market, support or service our customers, however, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

From time to time, we may be required to provide the Personal information we have gathered in response to a court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

It is possible that Mainstream Data, Inc. could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or their respective assets could be acquired. Should such a combination or acquisition occur, you should expect that Mainstream Data, Inc. would share some or all of your personal information to continue serving you and other users of our site.

## Confidentiality and Security

Mainstream Data, Inc. acknowledges your trust and is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To that end, we have implemented technology and processes in order to prevent Personal Information against loss and unauthorized use.

## Links to other Web sites

Certain portions of our Web site contain links to third-party Web sites to provide you with information relating to our business and associated activities. Once you have left the Mainstream Data, Inc.. site via these links, Mainstream Data, Inc.. is no longer responsible for the content and/or privacy policies of the respective sites.

## Updating Personal Information

You have the right to ensure the personal information collected about you is accurate and complete, and to request inaccurate or irrelevant information be corrected or deleted.

In the event your personal information has changed, you are encouraged to contact Mainstream Data, Inc.through E-mail at mainstreamdata.com and inform Mainstream Data, Inc. about the changes. You may also contact Mainstream Data, Inc.. any time through the above E-mail address to request to and verify that your personal information is accurate and up to date.

## Changes to Privacy Statement

Mainstream Data, Inc. reserves the right to change this privacy statement at any time. Any access to the Web site signifies that you agree to Mainstream Data, Inc. Policy current at that date. If you have any questions or concerns about our online privacy policy, please send an to [info@mainstreamdata.com](mailto:info@mainstreamdata.com)

Please contact us for more information.
